woobi.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Woobi

**Privacy Policy**

**_Who We Are_**

**Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)** _(‘ Woobi’ or ‘we’ or ‘us’ or ‘our’)_  is a programmatic in-game video advertising platform, serving users with targeted branded video content on behalf of brand advertisers and agencies. We process your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and in compliance with the relevant data protection Regulation and laws. This notice provides you with the necessary information regarding your rights and our obligations and explains how, why and when we process your personal data.

**Woobi’s  **registered office is at  **45 Rothschild St. Tel Aviv  **and we are a company registered in Israel under company number  **514234673.  **We act as the  **data processor/sub processor  **when processing your data **.**  Our designated Data Protection Officer  **Mr. Ben Lifshits**  can be contacted at ** **[ **DPO@woobi.com**](mailto:DPO@woobi.com) **.**

**_Information That We Process_**

**Woobi**  processes your personal information to meet our legal, statutory and/or contractual obligations and to provide you with our products and services. We will never collect nor process any unnecessary personal data from you and do not process your information in any way, other than as specified in this notice.

_The personal data that we receive about data subject (whether directly and/or from the data controller) comprises of:_

  * Cookie IDs
  * Device Advertising IDs
  * IP addresses
  * GPS coordinates
  * Browser data
  * User agent
  * mobile carrier
  * User demographic
  * User interests
  * Website URLs
  * App name and bundle ID
  * mobile device characteristics (such as OS, Device Make and device model)
  * and other non-directly identifiable information which is necessary for the purpose of serving an advertisement

Additionally, when downloading materials or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.  
**_The information is obtained in the below ways:  _**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, Use Live Chat, open a Support Ticket, Provide us with feedback on our products or services or enter information on our site.

Within the targeted advertising services, we provide, we collect the information through our advertising channels

  * **RTB** (real-time bidding) bid request – all data will be provided through the bid request and will be received from one of our controllers/processors
  * **Woobi Video Player**  – Data will be provided from a controller/processor, client base data such as IP address and user agent will be collected directly by Woobi
  * **Woobi SDK** – data will be provided from a controller/processor, device data such as advertising ID OS, OSV, IP address will be collected directly by Woobi.

**_How We Use Your Personal Data_**

**Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)**  takes your privacy very seriously and will never disclose or share your data without your consent; unless required to do so by law. We only process your data for as long as is necessary and for the purpose(s) specified in this notice. Where you have consented to us providing you with promotional offers and marketing, you are free to withdraw this consent at any time.   ** _The purposes and reasons for processing your personal data are detailed below: –_**

  * **Targeting** : for the purpose of serving ads that are more likely to be relevant to you based on the geo, demographic, interest, etc. data collected for this purpose.
  * **Frequency capping** : Making sure that you don’t see the same ad too many times.
  * **Fraud Identification and Prevention:  **to ensure our Advertisers’ ads are served to real users, and any measured metrics are not influenced by illegal or fraudulent activities.
  * **Monitoring and optimization** : Monitoring the results and performance of a campaign served on behalf of an Advertiser so that we can measure the result achieved and optimize both during the campaign duration as well as post-campaign.
  * **Reporting** : Providing our Advertisers with detailed reports as to the performance of their ads, including various campaign metrics and measurement KPI’s (impressions, click-through-rate, view-through rate, overall completion rate, conversions Reporting is made in an aggregated form, not on a per-user basis.

As for the information you directly opted into while using our website when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features, this information may be used in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**_Your Rights_**

You have the right to access any personal information that  **Social Tokens LTD. (DBA “Woobi”)**  processes about you and to request information about:

  * What personal data we process about you
  * The purposes of the processing
  * The categories of personal data concerned
  * The recipients to whom the personal data has/will be disclosed
  * How long we intend to store/process your personal data for, if any
  * If we did not collect the data directly from you, information about the source

If you believe that we hold any incomplete or inaccurate data about you, you have the right to ask us to correct and/or complete the information and we will strive to do so as quickly as possible; unless there is a valid reason for not doing so, at which point you will be notified.

You also have the right to request erasure of your personal data or to restrict processing ( _where applicable)_  in accordance with the data protection laws; as well as to object to any direct marketing from us. Where applicable, you have the right to data portability of your information and the right to be informed about any automated decision-making we may use, including:

  * Advertisement targeting and optimization
  * Real-time bidding on ad placements
  * Fraud identification and prevention

If we receive a request from you to exercise any of the above rights, we may ask you to verify your identity before acting on the request; this is to ensure that your data is protected and kept secure.

**_Sharing and Disclosing Your Personal Information_**

We do not share or disclose any of your personal information without your consent, other than for the purposes specified in this notice or where there is a legal requirement.  **Social Tokens LTD. (DBA “Woobi”)  **uses third parties to provide the below services and business functions; however, all processors acting on our behalf only process your data in accordance with instructions from us and comply fully with this privacy notice, the data protection laws and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  * **Demand partners–  **clients purchasing advertisement placements such as DSPs (Demand-side platforms), Agencies, Trading Desks, and Brand Advertisers.
  * **Fraud detection, prevention and control partners**
  * **DMPs (data management platforms) –  **for ad targeting and optimization

**_Safeguarding Measures_**

**Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)**  takes your privacy very seriously and takes every reasonable measure and precaution to protect and secure your personal data. We work hard to protect you and your information from unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction and have several layers of security measures in place, ** _  including: _**

  * SSL
  * Anonymization
  * Access Control (& Firewalls)
  * Data Transfer Encryption
  * Data Fragmentation & Segmentation

**_Transfers Outside the EU_**

**Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)  **transfers personal data outside of the EU in accordance with our International Data Transfer Policyץ

This policy is to be read in conjunction with our  ** _Data Protection Policy_**  and provides our procedures for transferring personal data outside the EU. We adhere to the Regulation for all non-EU transfers and have robust transfer safeguarding measures and controls in place to protect the personal data and the rights of the data subject in line with the Privacy Shield Framework Principles issued by the U.S. Department of Commerce, located at  _https://www.privacyshield.gov_   (“Privacy Shield Principles”) to all Personal Data that Company transfers to processors and/or sub-processors that originates from the European Economic Area or Switzerland (“EEA Data”).

Purposes for such transfer may include:

Region-based data processing on a global scale: our application is a global one and we have a data center in each one of our regions. Data is replicated through all the regions for reasons including processing within the region, fail-over, and reduced latency

Where we transfer personal information for the above reasons, we utilise any and all safeguarding measures and mechanisms to ensure that your personal data is always safe and secure. These measures can be found in our  **International Data Transfer Policy**.

**_Consequences of Not Providing Your Data_**

You are not obligated to provide your personal information to  **Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)** , however, as this information is required for us to provide you with our services, we will not be able to offer some/all our services without it.

**_Legitimate Interests_**

We occasionally process your personal information under the legitimate interests’ legal basis. Where this is the case, we have carried out a thorough Legitimate Interests’ Assessment (LIA) to ensure that we have weighed your interests and any risk posed to you against said interests; ensuring that they are proportionate and appropriate.

**_How Long We Keep Your Data_**

**Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)**  only ever retains personal information for as long as is necessary and we have strict review and retention policies in place to meet these obligations. We keep your basic personal data for a maximum 12 month per processed record after which time it will be destroyed.

Where you have consented to us using your details for direct marketing or opted into such service, we will keep such data until you notify us otherwise and/or withdraw your consent.

**_Marketing_**

Occasionally,  **Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)  **would like to contact you with product/service offerings, company news, industry updates, new platform features released, educational posts, promotion offers and more. If you consent to us using your contact details for this purpose, you have the right to modify or withdraw your consent at any time by using the opt-out/unsubscribe options or by contacting  **Social Tokens Ltd.  **directly.

If you  ** _consent_**  to us contacting you with the above-mentioned marketing and offers, please tick to say how you would like to be contacted:

Post ☐    Email ☐    Telephone ☐    Text Message (SMS) ☐    Automated Call ☐

**_General Purpose_**

**As stated at the top of this Privacy Policy,  **Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”) specializes in programmatic in-game video advertising, serving users with targeted branded video content on behalf of brand advertisers and agencies. These ads are served within websites, apps and/or games, and are personalized according to the user data we receive from different controllers such as publishers, supply partners, game developers and more, and may be collected directly by Social Tokens Ltd. (Woobi) as well, thus occasionally you will be presented with an advertisement which is targeted based on said data (as stipulated and solely for the purposes stated within this privacy policy).

Additionally, you may be presented with information, marketing material and/or promotion sent to you by email that has been identified as being beneficial to our customers and in our interests. Such information will be relevant to you as a customer and is non-intrusive and you will always have the option to opt-out/unsubscribe at any time.

**_Lodging A Complaint_**

**Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”)**  only processes your personal information in compliance with this privacy policy and in accordance with the relevant data protection laws. If, however you wish to raise a complaint regarding the processing of your personal data or are unsatisfied with how we have handled your information, you have the right to lodge a complaint either with our DPO, and/or with the supervisory authority.

Social Tokens Ltd.

Mr. Ben Lifshits, DPO

45 Rothschild St. Tel Aviv, Israel

**_Cookie_**

A  ** _‘cookie’_**  is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user’s computer by the user’s web browser while the user is browsing. When you visit a site that uses cookies for the first time, a cookie is downloaded onto your computer/mobile device so that the next time you visit that site, your device will remember useful information such as items added in the shopping cart, visited pages or logging in options.  
Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work or to work more efficiently, and our site relies on cookies to optimise user experience and for features and services to function properly.

Most web browsers allow some control to restrict or block cookies through the browser settings, however, if you disable cookies you may find this affects your ability to use certain parts of our website or services. For more information about cookies visit [https://www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).

On our programmatic platform, we may use cookies for user matching a common practice used for better ad targeting with our demand partners.  
__

**_Ongoing COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) Compliance_**

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) is a United States federal law that is designed to give parents control over the information collected from their young children online. COPPA prohibits the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information from children under 13 unless given parental consent. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites, apps, and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

Social Tokens Ltd. (DBA “Woobi”) operates in full compliance, in addition to GDPR, also with the COOPA requirements, and does not collect or process data from children under 13

Years of age. Woobi does not enable ads to be served on apps/websites that are directed at children under the age of 13 and holds its supply partners and publishers responsible for complying with these restrictions.

**_Contacting Us_**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

45 Rothschild St.

Tel Aviv, 6578401

Israel
